Daniel Schorr Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Broadcasts and Film, 1948-2006 (Box 21-93)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 32)
    - Special reports and programs (Box 50)
      - Twentieth Century (Box 53)
        - “The Plots Against Hitler,” 1963-1964, (3 folders) (Box 53)
        - “The Plots Against Hitler,” 1963-1964, (1 folder) (Box 54)
        - Poland, 1958-1959 (Box 54)
        - “The Strange Case of Rudolf Hess,” 1964-1965, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - “Who Killed Anne Frank,” 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 54)
      - Twenty-first Century Education, undated (Box 54)
      - Vlasov, Andreï Andreevich, 1962 (Box 54)
      - Watergate Affair
        - 1973 (Box 54)
          - June (Box 54)
          - July-Nov., (3 folders) (Box 55)
        - 1974 (Box 55)
      - What Are We Doing to Our Children? See also Container 50, A Boy Named Terry Egan (Box 55)
        - Background information, 1970-1973, (4 folders) (Box 55)
        - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 56)
        - Script, 1973 (Box 56)
      - What's the CIA All About? 1975 (Box 56)
    - Washington Bureau, Washington, D.C. (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 56)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 56)
        - Background information, 1971-1974, (2 folders) (Box 56)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1976, (3 folders) (Box 56)
        - Miscellany, 1972-1974 (Box 56)
        - Publicity, 1971-1973, (1 folder) (Box 56)
        - Publicity, 1971-1973, (1 folder) (Box 57)
      - Intelligence report leak (Box 57)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 57)
        - Miscellany, 1976, 1984 (Box 57)
        - Notes, 1976 (Box 57)
        - Publicity (Box 57)
          - 1976 (Box 57)
            - Feb.-Mar., (4 folders) (Box 57)
            - Apr.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 58)
          - 1977 (Box 58)
        - Scripts, 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 58)
        - Subpoena, 1976 (Box 59)
        - Testimonies, 1976 (Box 59)
      - Notes, 1967, 1974 (Box 59)
      - Publicity, 1972-1973 (Box 59)
      - Scripts (Box 59)
        - 1963-1966, (8 folders) (Box 59)
        - 1967, (8 folders) (Box 60)
        - 1968 (Box 60)
          - Jan.-Feb. (Box 60)
          - Mar.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 61)
        - 1969 (Box 61)
          - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders) (Box 61)
          - Mar.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 62)
        - 1970 (Box 62)
          - Jan.-Feb. (Box 62)
          - Mar.-Nov., (8 folders) (Box 63)
          - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 64)
        - 1971 (Box 64)
          - Jan.-May, (7 folders) (Box 64)
          - June-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 65)
          - Nov.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 66)
        - 1972 (Box 66)
          - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders) (Box 66)
          - May-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 67)
          - Dec. (Box 68)
        - 1973 (Box 68)
          - Jan.-July, (7 folders) (Box 68)
          - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 69)
        - 1974 (Box 69)
          - Jan.-May, (5 folders) (Box 69)
          - June-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 70)
        - 1975 (Box 70)
          - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders) (Box 70)
          - Apr.-Nov., (11 folders) (Box 71)
          - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 72)
        - 1976-1977, undated, (4 folders) (Box 72)
  - Discovery Channel (Box 72)
    - Nixon Scandals, 1994 (Box 72)
    - World War III, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Films
    - Elvis Meets Nixon, 1996 (Box 72)
    - The Game, 1996 (Box 72)
    - The Net, 1994-1995 (Box 72)
  - Gordon Freedman Productions, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
  - Independent Television News Association, 1978-1980, (4 folders) (Box 73)
  - KCET, Los Angeles, Calif., 1986 (Box 73)
  - KTCA, St. Paul, Minn., 1979 (Box 73)
  - Maryland Public Television, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Media Group Alaska, 1979-1986, (3 folders) (Box 73)
  - Michael Chait Media Consultants, 1986 (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous news reports and programs, 1948-1952, 1977-2002, (5 folders) (Box 74)
  - Mutual Broadcasting System, 1985-1990 (Box 74)
  - National Broadcasting Co., 1979-1986, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - National Public Radio (Box 74)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1995, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Program lists, 1971-1988 (Box 75)
    - Scripts (Box 75)
      - 1978-1983, (11 folders) (Box 75)
      - 1984-1986, (9 folders) (Box 76)
      - 1987 (Box 76)
        - Jan.-May, (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - June-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 77)
      - 1988 (Box 77)
        - Jan.-Sept., (5 folders) (Box 77)
        - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1989, (6 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1990, (11 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1991, (9 folders) (Box 80)
      - 1992 (Box 80)
        - Jan.-Apr., (2 folders) (Box 80)
        - May-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 81)
      - 1993 (Box 81)
        - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders) (Box 81)
        - Nov.-Dec. (Box 82)
      - 1994, (6 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1995 (Box 82)
        - Jan.-June, (3 folders) (Box 82)
        - July-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 83)
      - 1996, (6 folders) (Box 83)
      - 1997 (Box 83)
        - Jan.-Apr., (2 folders) (Box 83)
        - May-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 84)
      - 1998, (6 folders) (Box 84)
      - 1999, (6 folders) (Box 85)
      - 2000 (Box 85)
        - Jan.-June, (3 folders) (Box 85)
        - July-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 86)
      - 2001, (7 folders) (Box 86)
      - 2002, (6 folders) (Box 87)
      - 2003 (Box 87)
        - Jan.-Mar., (2 folders) (Box 87)
        - Apr.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 88)
      - 2004 (Box 88)
        - Jan.-Aug., (4 folders) (Box 88)
        - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 89)
      - 2005 (Box 89)
        - Jan.-July, (6 folders) (Box 89)
        - Aug.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 90)
      - 2006 (Box 90)
        - Jan.-July, (5 folders) (Box 90)
        - Aug.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 91)
      - Undated (Box 91)
  - PLC Media, 1985 (Box 91)
  - Public Broadcasting System, 1986 (Box 91)
  - Radio Nederland, 1948-1953, (3 folders) (Box 91)
  - University of West Florida, Pensacola, Fla., 1992-1993 (Box 91)
  - Viewpoint International, 1985-1986 (Box 92)
  - WETA, Washington, D.C., 1978-1979, 1985-1990, (4 folders) (Box 92)
  - WGBH, Boston, Mass., 1977-1982, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 92)
  - WISN, Milwaukee, Wis., 1979 (Box 92)
  - WNET, New York, N.Y. (Box 92)
    - 1978 (Box 92)
    - 1979 (Box 92)
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 92)
      - Mar.-June (Box 93)
    - 1985 (Box 93)
- Speeches and Public Appearances, 1956-2006 (Box 93-112)
  Background information, contracts, correspondence, interviews, notes, publicity, and texts of speeches for appearances as keynote speaker, conference participant, classroom lecturer, and panel moderator.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1956-1969, (12 folders) (Box 93)
  - 1970-1974 See also Oversize, (10 folders) (Box 94)
  - 1975, (6 folders) (Box 95)
  - 1976 (Box 95)
    - Feb.-Aug., (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - 1977, (5 folders) (Box 96)
  - 1978, (7 folders) (Box 97)
  - 1979-1980, (9 folders) (Box 98)
  - 1981-1983, (8 folders) (Box 99)
  - 1984, (4 folders) (Box 100)
  - 1985 (Box 100)
    - Feb.-Aug., (3 folders) (Box 100)
    - Oct.-Nov., (3 folders) (Box 101)
  - 1986, (7 folders) (Box 101)
  - 1987 (Box 101)
    - Jan. (Box 101)
    - Feb.-Dec. See also Oversize, (7 folders) (Box 102)
  - 1988 (Box 102)
    - Jan.-Apr. See also Oversize (Box 102)
    - May-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - 1989, (3 folders) (Box 103)
  - 1990, (8 folders) (Box 104)
  - 1991 (Box 105)
    - Jan.-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 105)
    - Sept.-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - 1992 (Box 106)
    - Jan.-May, (6 folders) (Box 106)
    - June-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 107)
  - 1993 (Box 107)
    - Feb.-Aug., (5 folders) (Box 107)
    - Sept.-Dec. (Box 107)
  - 1994 (Box 108)
    - Jan.-Aug., (6 folders) (Box 108)
    - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - 1995 (Box 109)
    - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders) (Box 109)
    - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - 1996-1997, (5 folders) (Box 110)
  - 1998-2000 See also Oversize, (11 folders) (Box 111)
  - 2001-2006, undated See also Oversize, (8 folders) (Box 112)
- Writings File, 1934-2005 (Box 113-137)
  Contracts, correspondence, clippings, drafts, publicity, and typescripts of Schorr's articles and books.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and therein alphabetically by title or name of publication.
  - Articles (Box 113)
    - Benelux articles, index, 1947-1953, (2 folders) (Box 113)
    - Bild, 1963-1964, 1985 (Box 113)
    - Channels of Communications, 1982-1986 (Box 113)
    - Christian Science Monitor (Box 113)
      - Clippings (Box 113)
        - 1948-1950, (6 folders) (Box 113)
        - 1951-1955, 1967, 1986-2000, (12 folders) (Box 114)
        - 2001-2005, (4 folders) (Box 115)
      - Typescripts (Box 115)
        - 1948, (4 folders) (Box 115)
        - 1949 (Box 115)
          - Jan.-Mar., (2 folders) (Box 115)
          - Apr.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 116)
        - 1950 (Box 116)
          - Jan.-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 116)
          - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 117)
        - 1951-1953, undated, (10 folders) (Box 117)
    - Daily Mail (Box 117)
      - 1949 (Box 117)
        - Feb.-July, (3 folders) (Box 117)
        - Aug.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 118)
      - 1950-1951, (12 folders) (Box 118)
      - 1952-1953, (8 folders) (Box 119)
    - “Daniel Schorr at Large” (Box 119)
      - 1978 (Box 119)
        - Feb.-June, (5 folders) (Box 119)
        - July-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 120)
      - 1979 (Box 120)
        - Jan.-May, (5 folders) (Box 120)
        - June-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 121)
      - 1980, (5 folders) (Box 121)
    - Esquire, 1983 (Box 121)
    - Freelance log, 1948-1953 (Box 122)
    - Groene Amsterdammer, 1949-1950, (4 folders) (Box 122)
    - Grolier, circa 1964 (Box 122)
    - High Times, 1978-1979 (Box 122)
    - Ixtlan, 1995 (Box 122)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1985, 1993 (Box 122)
    - Miscellaneous articles and scrapbooks (Box 122)
      - 1934-1967, 1974-1998 See also Oversize, (6 folders) (Box 122)
      - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - More, 1977-1978 (Box 123)
    - Neue Illustrierte, 1963 (Box 123)
    - New Leader, 1959-1966, 1972-1994, 2005 (Box 123)
    - New Republic, 1965, 1980 (Box 123)
    - New York Times (Box 123)
      - Abstracts, 1971-1981 (Box 123)
      - Clippings, 1947-1960, 1974-1977, (5 folders) (Box 123)
      - Typescripts (Box 124)
        - 1949-1951, (8 folders) (Box 124)
        - 1952 (Box 124)
          - Jan.-July, (5 folders) (Box 124)
          - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 125)
        - 1953, 1966, 1976-1977, 1989-1995, (5 folders) (Box 125)
    - Newsday, 1994 (Box 125)
    - Newsweek, 1957, 1976, 1989-1994 (Box 125)
    - Progressive, 1976-1986 (Box 125)
    - Reader's Digest, 1967 (Box 126)
    - Reporter, 1959-1963 (Box 126)
    - Rolling Stone, 1975-1977, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Saturday Review, 1963, 1979 (Box 126)
    - Syndicated columns, 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - This Week, 1958-1963 (Box 126)
    - Time, 1960 (Box 127)
    - Time-Life International, 1948 (Box 127)
    - TV Guide, 1984 (Box 127)
    - United States Information Service, 1948 (Box 127)
    - Village Voice, 1978, 1986 (Box 127)
    - Washington Post, 1957, 1964-1966, 1973-1980, 1986-1995, (2 folders) (Box 127)
    - Washingtonian, 1981-1982, (3 folders) (Box 127)
  - Books
    - Clearing the Air (Box 127)
      - Background information, 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Background information, 1976-1977, (1 folder) (Box 128)
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1976-1979, (4 folders) (Box 128)
      - Drafts (Box 128)
        - 1976 (Box 128)
        - 1977 (Box 128)
          - Jan. (Box 128)
          - Feb., (3 folders) (Box 128)
          - Feb., (8 folders) (Box 129)
          - Feb., (2 folders) (Box 130)
          - Mar.-Apr., (7 folders) (Box 130)
          - Mar.-Apr., (5 folders) (Box 131)
          - May, (2 folders) (Box 131)
          - May, (2 folders) (Box 132)
          - circa June, (4 folders) (Box 132)
        - 1978 (Box 133)
          - Paperback edition (Box 133)
          - Second edition (Box 133)
        - Undated (Box 133)
          - Bibliography and index (Box 133)
          - Miscellaneous pages (Box 133)
      - Galley proofs, 1977 (Box 133)
      - Notes, undated (Box 133)
      - Photographs and cartoons, 1973-1976 (Box 133)
      - Publicity (Box 133)
        - Articles and news releases (Box 133)
          - 1976 (Box 133)
          - 1977 (Box 133)
            - Feb.-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 133)
            - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 133)
          - 1978, (2 folders) (Box 134)
        - Book parties, 1977-1978 (Box 134)
        - Distribution lists, 1977 (Box 134)
        - Promotional tours, 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 134)
    - Don't Get Sick in America, 1970-1973 (Box 134)
    - Introduction to Taking the Stand by Oliver L. North, 1987 (Box 134)
    - Staying Tuned: A Life in Journalism (Box 134)
      - Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 134)
      - Correspondence, 1994-2001 (Box 134)
      - Drafts (Box 135)
        - 1996-2000, (6 folders) (Box 135)
        - Undated, (4 folders) (Box 136)
      - Notes, undated, (2 folders) (Box 136)
      - Outlines, undated (Box 136)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box 136)
      - Publicity and reviews (Box 136)
        - 1994 (Box 136)
        - 2001 (Box 136)
          - Jan.-Apr. (Box 136)
          - May-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 137)
        - 2002 (Box 137)
      - Royalty statements, 2001 (Box 137)
- Subject File, 1933-2004 (Box 137-182)
  Correspondence, legal documents, news clippings, reports, and printed material.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Abrams, Elliott, 1986-1987 (Box 137)
  - Alaska, 1972-1979 (Box 137)
  - Albright, Madeleine K., 1996-2001 (Box 137)
  - Alcoholism, 1966 (Box 137)
  - Allen, Richard V., 1971-1989, (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - Alps, 1987 (Box 138)
  - Amnesty, 1974 (Box 138)
  - Anderson, Jack, 1972-1978 (Box 138)
  - Angleton, James (Box 138)
    - Biography by Michael Holzman, 2004, (5 folders) (Box 138)
    - Miscellany, 1975-1991 (Box 138)
  - Angola, 1975-1976 (Box 139)
  - Arms control, 1961-1965, 1974, 1987 (Box 139)
  - Assassinations, 1973-1979 (Box 139)
  - Austria, 1980 (Box 139)
  - Baldwin, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 139)
  - Barth, Alan, 1977-1979 (Box 139)
  - Bazelon, David L., 1974-1993 (Box 139)
  - Berger, Samuel R., undated (Box 139)
  - Blackmun, Harry A., 1982-1999 (Box 139)
  - Bloch, Felix S., 1989-2001 (Box 139)
  - Bohlen, Charles E., 1956-1957 (Box 139)
  - Boland amendment, 1985-1987 (Box 139)
  - Boorda, Michael, 1996 (Box 139)
  - Bork, Robert H., 1987-1988 (Box 139)
  - Bourne, Peter Geoffry, 1978 (Box 139)
  - Brucan, Silvia, 1988-1990 (Box 139)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1970-1981 (Box 139)
  - Buchanan, Patrick J., 1972-1992 (Box 140)
  - Buckley, William F., 1986-1987 (Box 140)
  - Burger, Warren E., 1969 (Box 140)
  - Bush, George W., 1975-1993, (6 folders) (Box 140)
  - Bush, George W., 1975-1993, (1 folder) (Box 141)
  - Cable television, 1978-1985 (Box 141)
  - Calero, Adolfo, 1987 (Box 141)
  - Califano, Joseph A., 1973-1992 (Box 141)
  - Campus unrest, 1969 (Box 141)
  - Caplin, Mortimer M., 1991, 2000 (Box 141)
  - Carter, Billy See Container 161, Lance, Bert (Box 141)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976-1980 (Box 141)
  - Casey, William J., 1972, 1980-1987, (2 folders) (Box 141)
  - Castillo, Thomas, 1987 (Box 142)
  - Castro, Fidel, 1966, 1975-1978 (Box 142)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 142)
    - Chile, operations in, 1971-1978 (Box 142)
    - Reform (Box 142)
      - Congressional hearings, 1975-1978 (Box 142)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 142)
      - Legislation, 1974-1978 (Box 142)
      - Miscellany, 1975-1981 (Box 142)
      - News clippings, 1972-1996, (5 folders) (Box 143)
      - Notes, circa 1975-1978 (Box 143)
      - Press briefings, 1975-1980 (Box 143)
      - Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 144)
  - Clarridge, Duane (“Dewey”), 1983-1987 (Box 144)
  - Clifford, Clark M., 1991 (Box 144)
  - Cline, Ray S., 1977 (Box 144)
  - Clinton, Bill, impeachment of, 1998 (Box 144)
  - Colby, William E., 1973-1978 (Box 144)
  - Colson, Charles W., 1972-1978 (Box 144)
  - Common Cause, 1972-1973 (Box 144)
  - Conein, Lucien, 1971-1977 (Box 144)
  - Connally, John B., 1970-1988 (Box 144)
  - Cooper, Charles J., 1986-1987 (Box 145)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1981-1989, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 145)
  - Counterfeit money, 1975 (Box 145)
  - Covert operations, 1973-1998, (2 folders) (Box 145)
  - Cuba, Bay of Pigs Invasion, fortieth anniversary conference (Box 145)
    - Declassified documents, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - Declassified documents, 2001, (1 folder) (Box 146)
    - International documentation, 2001 (Box 146)
    - Selected secondary readings, 2001 (Box 146)
  - Cuban missile crisis (1962), 1971-1989 (Box 146)
  - Cults, 1977, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Cuomo, Mario M., 1986-1987 (Box 146)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1964-1968, 1999 (Box 146)
  - Dairy industry, 1969-1974, (2 folders) (Box 146)
  - Daniloff, Nicholas S., 1979-1986 (Box 146)
  - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 1986 (Box 147)
  - De Mohrenschildt, George, 1977 (Box 147)
  - Dean, John W., 1973 (Box 147)
  - Debategate, 1980-1983 (Box 147)
  - Defectors, 1985-1986 (Box 147)
  - Democratic Party, 1972 (Box 147)
  - Desegregation, 1966-1972 (Box 147)
  - DeWitt Clinton High School, New York, N.Y., 1933, 1984-1987 (Box 147)
  - Dobrynin, Anatoly F., 1984 (Box 147)
  - Dole, Bob, 1970 (Box 147)
  - Donovan, Raymond J., 1982, (2 folders) (Box 147)
  - Donovan, Raymond J., 1982, (4 folders) (Box 148)
  - Drugs, 1967-1968 (Box 148)
  - Dutton, Robert C., 1986-1987 (Box 148)
  - Eastern Europe, 1989 (Box 148)
  - Edelman, Marian and Peter, 1974, 1993 (Box 148)
  - Education, 1969 (Box 148)
  - Egeberg, Roger O., 1969-1970 (Box 148)
  - Ehrlichman, John, 1971-1978 (Box 149)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1990 (Box 149)
  - Eisenhower, Susan, 1990 (Box 149)
  - Electronic surveillance, 1975-1979, (2 folders) (Box 149)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel, 1976-1978, 1997 (Box 149)
  - Epstein, Edward Jay, 1963-1978, (2 folders) (Box 149)
  - Erhard, Ludwig, 1965-1966 (Box 149)
  - Ethics in government, 1970 (Box 149)
  - Family issues and public policy (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 149)
    - Miscellany, 1978 (Box 149)
    - News articles, 1976-1980, (2 folders) (Box 149)
    - News releases, 1976-1979 (Box 150)
    - Newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 150)
    - Notes, 1977-1979, (2 folders) (Box 150)
    - Presidential Documents, 1977-1979 (Box 150)
    - Reports and position statements, 1972-1979, undated, (5 folders) (Box 150)
  - Farmer, James, undated (Box 151)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1966-1978 (Box 151)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1984 (Box 151)
  - Fiers, Alan, 1987 (Box 151)
  - FitzGerald, Desmond, 1966 (Box 151)
  - Fletcher, James C., 1971 (Box 151)
  - Food additives, 1969-1972 (Box 151)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1972-2000, (2 folders) (Box 151)
  - Fortas, Abe, 1969-1982 (Box 151)
  - Frank, Anne, undated (Box 151)
  - Freedom of information, 1975-1977 (Box 151)
  - Freedom of the press, 1972-1985, (2 folders) (Box 152)
  - Friendly, Fred W., 1973-1978, 1998 (Box 152)
  - Garbo, Greta, 1990 (Box 152)
  - Gardner, John W., 1986 (Box 152)
  - Garment, Leonard, 1988 (Box 152)
  - Germany (Box 152)
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1961-1963 (Box 152)
    - Berlin air corridors, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Berlin Wall escape tunnel, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Espionage, 1962-1963, 1985-1986 (Box 152)
    - Foreign relations, 1966-1968 (Box 152)
    - Miscellany, 1960-1966, 1986 (Box 152)
    - Press seminar, 1964 (Box 152)
  - Gertz, Bill, 1995-1999 (Box 152)
  - Ghorbanifar, Manucher, 1987 (Box 152)
  - Glomar Explorer (submarine ship), 1972-1977 (Box 153)
  - Goldberg, Arthur J., 1989-1990 (Box 153)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1964-1967, 1975, 1998 (Box 153)
  - Gray mail, 1978 (Box 153)
  - Gregg, Donald P., 1989 (Box 153)
  - Guns, undated (Box 153)
  - Haass, Richard N., 1999-2002 (Box 153)
  - Haig, Alexander M., 1978-1983, 1999 (Box 153)
  - Hakim, Albert A., 1987 (Box 153)
  - Haldeman, H. R., 1970-1978 (Box 153)
  - Hall, Fawn, 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 153)
  - Hall, Fawn, 1984-1987, (1 folder) (Box 154)
  - Health, 1966-1974 (Box 154)
  - Helms, Jesse, 1984-1986 (Box 154)
  - Helms, Richard M., 1975-1978, (2 folders) (Box 154)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 154)
  - Hersh, Seymour, 1981-2001 (Box 154)
  - Hinckley, John W., 1981-1985, 1997, (3 folders) (Box 154)
  - Hinckley, John W., 1981-1985, 1997, (1 folder) (Box 155)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1992-1993 (Box 155)
  - Hostages, 1990 (Box 155)
  - Hugel, Max, 1981-1983 (Box 155)
  - Hughes, Howard, 1968-1976, (2 folders) (Box 155)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1968 (Box 155)
  - Hungary, 1965-1969 (Box 155)
  - Hunger, 1968-1971 (Box 155)
  - Hunt, E. Howard, 1971-1977 (Box 155)
  - Hussein, King of Jordan, 1975-1977 (Box 155)
  - Huston Plan, 1964-1975 (Box 155)
  - Hydrogen bombs, 1979 (Box 155)
  - Indonesia, 1948, 1985 (Box 155)
  - Inman, Bobbie Ray, 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box 156)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1967-1975 (Box 156)
  - Iran, 1979-1988 (Box 156)
  - Iran-Contra Affair (Box 156)
    - Biographies, 1987 (Box 156)
    - Declassified documents, 1986-1993, (4 folders) (Box 156)
    - Declassified documents, 1986-1993, (6 folders) (Box 157)
    - Declassified documents, 1986-1993, (2 folders) (Box 158)
    - Miscellany, 1986-1993, (3 folders) (Box 158)
    - News clippings, 1986-1993, (2 folders) (Box 158)
  - Israel, 1982-1988 (Box 159)
  - Italy, 1976 (Box 159)
  - ITT, 1972 (Box 159)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1994 (Box 159)
  - Jewish Telegraph Agency, 1997 (Box 159)
  - John Paul II, assassination attempt, 1982-1986 (Box 159)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1966 (Box 159)
  - Juliana, Queen of the Netherlands (Box 159)
    - 1941-1952 (Box 159)
    - 1955, 1977-1982, 2001 (Box 159)
  - Juvenile delinquency, 1967 (Box 159)
  - Kalmbach, Herbert, 1973 (Box 159)
  - Kampelman, Max M., 1967, 1978-1981 (Box 159)
  - Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1978-1988 (Box 159)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1993, (1 folder) (Box 159)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1993, (3 folders) (Box 160)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1993 (Box 160)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich, 1955-1961, 1988-1989 (Box 160)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Kirkland, Lane, 1979 (Box 160)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1971-1976, 1999 (Box 160)
  - Kleindienst, Richard D., 1973-1978 (Box 161)
  - Koczak, Stephen A., 1967, 1990 (Box 161)
  - Koop, C. Everett, 1987 (Box 161)
  - Korea, 1975-1978 (Box 161)
  - Kurds, 1966, 1974-1982 (Box 161)
  - Labor, 1967 (Box 161)
  - Laitin, Joseph, 2002 (Box 161)
  - Lance, Bert and Billy Carter, 1978-1979 (Box 161)
  - Lebanon, 1981-1984 (Box 161)
  - Leningrad, Soviet Union, 1956 (Box 161)
  - Levin, Jeremy, 1985 (Box 161)
  - Libel, 1981-1984 (Box 161)
  - Liddy, G. Gordon, 1974-1981 (Box 161)
  - MacFarlane, Robert C., 1985-1991 (Box 161)
  - Mafia, 1971-1977, (2 folders) (Box 161)
  - Malek, Fred, 1972 (Box 161)
  - Malpractice insurance, 1970 (Box 161)
  - Mankiewicz, Frank, 1982 (Box 161)
  - Marshall Plan, 1997 (Box 161)
  - McCord, James, 1980 (Box 161)
  - McGovern, George, 1971, 1978-1985, 1993 (Box 162)
  - McNamara, Robert S., 1983-1997 (Box 162)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1982-1987 (Box 162)
  - Metzenbaum, Howard, 1987 (Box 162)
  - Michalowski, Jerzy, 1997 (Box 162)
  - Middle East, 1982-1985 (Box 162)
  - Mills, Wilbur, 1971 (Box 162)
  - Mitchell, John N., 1973 (Box 162)
  - Model cities, 1969 (Box 162)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., undated (Box 162)
  - Music, 1955-1958 (Box 162)
  - Nazis, undated (Box 162)
  - Netherlands, 1952-1953, 1965-1966, 1992-1993, (1 folder) (Box 162)
  - Netherlands, 1952-1953, 1965-1966, 1992-1993, (1 folder) (Box 163)
  - New World Order, 1991 (Box 163)
  - New York, N.Y., 1966 (Box 163)
  - Nicaragua, 1987-1990 (Box 163)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 163)
    - Death, 1994 (Box 163)
    - Impeachment, 1974 (Box 163)
      - May-June, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 163, Box 164)